this channel is not about climbing
originally it was a documentary of my
journey of learning dozens of new skills
as quickly as possible although it has
somewhat evolved it's still very focused
on self-development learning and
challenging myself but around two years
ago I tried climbing just as another
skill for a video and fell deeply madly
hopelessly in love and since then I just
can't stop climbing seriously I just
can't help myself we made four videos on
this channel about climbing and we were
really starting to get into the weeds
with it it was starting to get pretty
Technical and at this point the audience
was like okay we get it you like
climbing but this isn't actually what we
signed up for and I get it to just focus
on one thing here on this channel is not
really true to the identity of the
channel so from here on out no more I am
done with climbing videos finished the
end on this channel anyway we've
actually been making so much climbing
content that I've started an entirely
new and separate Channel simply called
Mike Boyd climbs we've already had Tom
Randall Matt Wright Dave McLoud and
Hannah Morris on as guests it features
bouldering sport both indoors and
Outdoors as well as some Trad climbing
too and really some of the content on
there they are some of my favorite
videos that I've most proud of so for
those of you who are interested in
climbing in any way go check out the new
channel and for those of you who aren't
don't worry no more climbing content on
this channel regular content from here
on out I promise I just want to say
thanks for sticking with me throughout
this despite my uh capricious Tendencies
I hope you guys understand sometimes you
just get hooked anyway please go check
out the climbing Channel if you are
interested and don't worry about it if
you're not thank you very much for
watching and I'll catch you here soon
peace